let questions = [{"numb": 1, "question": "Aufmerksamkeit", "answer": "attention, Gamana", "options": ["attention, Gamana", "dignified", "defeat, solu", "Krama, Measure"]}, {"numb": 2, "question": "Konvertierung", "answer": "Covert (Religion)", "options": ["Covert (Religion)", "Nature", "special, visheshavada", "opposition,"]}, {"numb": 3, "question": "Digitalizierung", "answer": "Digitalization", "options": ["Oxygen", "active, sakriya, chatuvatikeyindiru", "compulsory", "Digitalization"]}, {"numb": 4, "question": "Beglaubigte", "answer": "pramaanikarisida, dhrudikarisida", "options": ["Kaavos, Kannda: Gondala", "necessary, required", "pramaanikarisida, dhrudikarisida", "meanwhile, ee naduve, ashtralli"]}, {"numb": 5, "question": "Hindernis", "answer": "obstacle, ade tade", "options": ["Digitalization", "purposefully, uddeshapporvakavagi", "obstacle, ade tade", "deadly"]}, {"numb": 6, "question": "Meinung", "answer": "opinion, abhipraya", "options": ["obstacle, ade tade", "loneliness", "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "opinion, abhipraya"]}, {"numb": 7, "question": "Perspektiv", "answer": "prespective, Viewpoint, Drustikona", "options": ["prespective, Viewpoint, Drustikona", "according to..", "Kaavos, Kannda: Gondala", "meanwhile, ee naduve, ashtralli"]}, {"numb": 8, "question": "Anwendung", "answer": "usage  Kannada: BaLake,", "options": ["usage  Kannada: BaLake,", "approval", "dignity, Ghanathe", "sight, drushti"]}, {"numb": 9, "question": "t\u00f6dlich", "answer": "deadly", "options": ["necessary, required", "deadly", "KaruNe, Daye", "communal, komu"]}, {"numb": 10, "question": "w\u00fcrdig", "answer": "dignified", "options": ["dignified", "Pressure", "Carbon monooxide", "special, visheshavada"]}, {"numb": 11, "question": "elementar", "answer": "basic, fundamental", "options": ["Blessings, verb is SegNen", "necessary, required", "Nature", "basic, fundamental"]}, {"numb": 12, "question": "wesentlich", "answer": "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "options": ["Opportunity", "abhivraddhi, progress", "active, sakriya, chatuvatikeyindiru", "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi"]}, {"numb": 13, "question": "inzwischen", "answer": "meanwhile, ee naduve, ashtralli", "options": ["Victory, Jaya", "meanwhile, ee naduve, ashtralli", "Procedure", "KaruNe, Daye"]}, {"numb": 14, "question": "Richtlinie", "answer": "Guideline, Kannada: Maargasoochi", "options": ["opposition,", "opinion, view, abhipraya, nota", "Guideline, Kannada: Maargasoochi", "according to.."]}, {"numb": 15, "question": "Pflicht", "answer": "compulsory", "options": ["resource, sampanmoola", "compulsory", "illegal, kanoonu bahira", "process, kannada: prakriye"]}, {"numb": 16, "question": "Menschheit", "answer": "humanity", "options": ["prerequisites, \u0caa\u0cc2\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0caa\u0cc7\u0c95\u0ccd\u0cb7\u0cbf\u0ca4\u0c97\u0cb3\u0cc1", "strategy", "temporary, taatkalika", "humanity"]}, {"numb": 17, "question": "Strategie", "answer": "strategy", "options": ["Hectic", "strategy", "peace, shaanti", "Cheat, Vanchane, Mosa"]}, {"numb": 18, "question": "Betrieb", "answer": "operations, business, firm", "options": ["Infrastructure", "Pressure", "operations, business, firm", "communal, komu"]}, {"numb": 19, "question": "Randale", "answer": "Riot, galabhe", "options": ["pramaanikarisida, dhrudikarisida", "Riot, galabhe", "usage  Kannada: BaLake,", "operations, business, firm"]}, {"numb": 20, "question": "prinzipiell", "answer": "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "options": ["pramaanikarisida, dhrudikarisida", "corresponding, anuroopavada", "illegal, kanoonu bahira", "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi"]}, {"numb": 21, "question": "Ablauf", "answer": "Procedure", "options": ["Procedure", "permanent, shashwata", "sign", "Victory, Jaya"]}, {"numb": 22, "question": "Betrug", "answer": "Cheat, Vanchane, Mosa", "options": ["waste, garbage", "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "Cheat, Vanchane, Mosa", "affected, concerned, baadhitha"]}, {"numb": 23, "question": "Ressource", "answer": "resource, sampanmoola", "options": ["dignified", "resource, sampanmoola", "available, kannada : Labhyavide, Doraku", "joy, santosha"]}, {"numb": 24, "question": "Sauerstoff", "answer": "Oxygen", "options": ["violent, himsatmaka", "Oxygen", "peace, shaanti", "Globalization"]}, {"numb": 25, "question": "Absicht", "answer": "puprose, uddeesha", "options": ["puprose, uddeesha", "Oxygen", "political, raajakiya", "defeat, solu"]}, {"numb": 26, "question": "pl\u00f6tzlich", "answer": "suddenly, idakiddante, akaasmat", "options": ["Carbon monooxide", "marketing", "basic, fundamental", "suddenly, idakiddante, akaasmat"]}, {"numb": 27, "question": "durchschnitt", "answer": "sarasari", "options": ["pramaanikarisida, dhrudikarisida", "KaruNe, Daye", "Riot, galabhe", "sarasari"]}, {"numb": 28, "question": "Verf\u00fcgbar", "answer": "available, kannada : Labhyavide, Doraku", "options": ["area, Bhoopradesha", "available, kannada : Labhyavide, Doraku", "logic, tarka", "reluctant, manasillada"]}, {"numb": 29, "question": "betroffene", "answer": "affected, concerned, baadhitha", "options": ["affected, concerned, baadhitha", "peace, shaanti", "basic, fundamental", "abuse, DurbaLake"]}, {"numb": 30, "question": "Bereich", "answer": "area, Kshetra", "options": ["Nature", "opinion, view, abhipraya, nota", "area, Kshetra", "joyful, santoshadayaka"]}, {"numb": 31, "question": "brutal", "answer": "violent, himsatmaka", "options": ["violent, himsatmaka", "permanent, shashwata", "dignity, Ghanathe", "Victory, Jaya"]}, {"numb": 32, "question": "widerwillig", "answer": "reluctant, manasillada", "options": ["spokesperson, vaktaar", "necessary, required", "reluctant, manasillada", "contact person, samparka vyakti"]}, {"numb": 33, "question": "Fachbereich", "answer": "department, vibhaga", "options": ["department, vibhaga", "Krama, Measure", "Carbon monooxide", "Victory, Jaya"]}, {"numb": 34, "question": "\u00fcbersicht", "answer": "overview, pakshinota, avalokana", "options": ["overview, pakshinota, avalokana", "department, ilaakhe", "illegal, kanoonu bahira", "corresponding, anuroopavada"]}, {"numb": 35, "question": "Ansicht", "answer": "opinion, view, abhipraya, nota", "options": ["constantly, nirantaravagi", "overview, pakshinota, avalokana", "Kannda: BaLake", "opinion, view, abhipraya, nota"]}, {"numb": 36, "question": "Klima", "answer": "Nature", "options": ["special, visheshavada", "attention, Gamana", "department, vibhaga", "Nature"]}, {"numb": 37, "question": "Froh", "answer": "joyful, santoshita", "options": ["prerequisites, \u0caa\u0cc2\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0caa\u0cc7\u0c95\u0ccd\u0cb7\u0cbf\u0ca4\u0c97\u0cb3\u0cc1", "humanity", "area, Kshetra", "joyful, santoshita"]}, {"numb": 38, "question": "Schild, Schilder", "answer": "sign", "options": ["sign", "attentive", "Krama, Measure", "puprose, uddeesha"]}, {"numb": 39, "question": "entsprechende", "answer": "corresponding, anuroopavada", "options": ["constantly, nirantaravagi", "abhivraddhi, progress", "corresponding, anuroopavada", "overview, pakshinota, avalokana"]}, {"numb": 40, "question": "ben\u00f6tigt", "answer": "necessary, required", "options": ["necessary, required", "prerequisites, \u0caa\u0cc2\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0caa\u0cc7\u0c95\u0ccd\u0cb7\u0cbf\u0ca4\u0c97\u0cb3\u0cc1", "abhivraddhi, progress", "obstacle, ade tade"]}, {"numb": 41, "question": "Infrastruktur", "answer": "Infrastructure", "options": ["Infrastructure", "communal, komu", "abuse, DurbaLake", "department, ilaakhe"]}, {"numb": 42, "question": "Voraussetzung", "answer": "prerequisites, \u0caa\u0cc2\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0caa\u0cc7\u0c95\u0ccd\u0cb7\u0cbf\u0ca4\u0c97\u0cb3\u0cc1", "options": ["peaceful, shaantiyuta", "permanent, shashwata", "prerequisites, \u0caa\u0cc2\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0caa\u0cc7\u0c95\u0ccd\u0cb7\u0cbf\u0ca4\u0c97\u0cb3\u0cc1", "Kannda: BaLake"]}, {"numb": 43, "question": "Sieg", "answer": "Victory, Jaya", "options": ["Victory, Jaya", "Hectic", "joyful, nagumogada", "Riot, galabhe"]}, {"numb": 44, "question": "Prozess", "answer": "process, kannada: prakriye", "options": ["Opportunity", "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "department, ilaakhe", "process, kannada: prakriye"]}, {"numb": 45, "question": "Sprecher/in", "answer": "spokesperson, vaktaar", "options": ["Pressure", "spokesperson, vaktaar", "opinion, view, abhipraya, nota", "loneliness"]}, {"numb": 46, "question": "widernat\u00fcrlich", "answer": "against nature, aswabhavika", "options": ["against nature, aswabhavika", "Carbon monooxide", "resource, sampanmoola", "abuse, DurbaLake"]}, {"numb": 47, "question": "Feindschaft", "answer": "enmity, Vairatva", "options": ["enmity, Vairatva", "adjective, Perfect, paripoorna", "Infrastructure", "illegal, kanoonu bahira"]}, {"numb": 48, "question": "gewaltsam", "answer": "violent, himsatmaka", "options": ["violent, himsatmaka", "friendship", "Policy", "opposition,"]}, {"numb": 49, "question": "Kohlenstoff", "answer": "Carbon", "options": ["Carbon", "No response given", "available, kannada : Labhyavide, Doraku", "compulsory"]}, {"numb": 50, "question": "widerspruch", "answer": "opposition,", "options": ["abuse, DurbaLake", "opposition,", "prerequisites, \u0caa\u0cc2\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0caa\u0cc7\u0c95\u0ccd\u0cb7\u0cbf\u0ca4\u0c97\u0cb3\u0cc1", "suddenly, idakiddante, akaasmat"]}, {"numb": 51, "question": "Qual", "answer": "torture, chitrahimse", "options": ["Enviornment friendly", "torture, chitrahimse", "caution, precaution, ecchara, jagarookate", "attention, Gamana"]}, {"numb": 52, "question": "verbrauch", "answer": "kannada: Sevane, consumption", "options": ["purposefully, uddeshapporvakavagi", "caution, precaution, ecchara, jagarookate", "reluctant, manasillada", "kannada: Sevane, consumption"]}, {"numb": 53, "question": "Stoff", "answer": "Fuel, Indhana", "options": ["Occupation", "forever, shashwata", "Fuel, Indhana", "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi"]}, {"numb": 54, "question": "widerrechtlich", "answer": "illegal, kanoonu bahira", "options": ["combination", "Kaavos, Kannda: Gondala", "illegal, kanoonu bahira", "defeat, solu"]}, {"numb": 55, "question": "illegal", "answer": "illegal, kanoonu bahira", "options": ["Former, maaji", "Hectic", "special, visheshavada", "illegal, kanoonu bahira"]}, {"numb": 56, "question": "M\u00fcll", "answer": "garbage", "options": ["Carbon monooxide", "garbage", "serious, Gambhira", "Oxygen"]}, {"numb": 57, "question": "logik", "answer": "logic, tarka", "options": ["logic, tarka", "sign", "marketing", "compulsory"]}, {"numb": 58, "question": "Gelegenheit", "answer": "Opportunity", "options": ["involvement", "available, kannada : Labhyavide, Doraku", "area, Bhoopradesha", "Opportunity"]}, {"numb": 59, "question": "Besch\u00e4ftigung", "answer": "Occupation", "options": ["need, Avashyakate", "Occupation", "area, Kshetra", "available, kannada : Labhyavide, Doraku"]}, {"numb": 60, "question": "Fehlerlos", "answer": "without problems", "options": ["strategy", "impaired, disabled", "without problems", "imprint, kaalachchu, Mudre"]}, {"numb": 61, "question": "Bed\u00fcrfnis", "answer": "need, Avashyakate", "options": ["reluctant, manasillada", "loneliness", "need, Avashyakate", "basic, fundamental"]}, {"numb": 62, "question": "Ma\u00dfnahme", "answer": "Krama, Measure", "options": ["contact person, samparka vyakti", "Kannda: BaLake", "KaruNe, Daye", "Krama, Measure"]}, {"numb": 63, "question": "sofort", "answer": "imemdiately, tatkshana", "options": ["dignified", "imemdiately, tatkshana", "Pressure", "similar, holuva, samavada"]}, {"numb": 64, "question": "Freude", "answer": "joy, santosha", "options": ["logic, tarka", "lonely", "Blessings, verb is SegNen", "joy, santosha"]}, {"numb": 65, "question": "durchsichtig", "answer": "transparent, paradarhska", "options": ["improvment", "transparent, paradarhska", "corresponding, anuroopavada", "non violence, ahimse"]}, {"numb": 66, "question": "Gewalt", "answer": "violence, Himse, dourjanya", "options": ["enmity, Vairatva", "Digitalization", "suddenly, idakiddante, akaasmat", "violence, Himse, dourjanya"]}, {"numb": 67, "question": "Abnutzung", "answer": "abuse, DurbaLake", "options": ["abuse, DurbaLake", "Hate, Dwesha", "Procedure", "Modernization"]}, {"numb": 68, "question": "besondere", "answer": "special, visheshavada", "options": ["pramaanikarisida, dhrudikarisida", "Krama, Measure", "joy, santosha", "special, visheshavada"]}, {"numb": 69, "question": "Druck", "answer": "Pressure", "options": ["illegal, kanoonu bahira", "Pressure", "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "suddenly, idakiddante, akaasmat"]}, {"numb": 70, "question": "Lebensw\u00fcrdigkeit", "answer": "KaruNe, Daye", "options": ["without problems", "violence, Himse, dourjanya", "KaruNe, Daye", "forever, shashwata"]}, {"numb": 71, "question": "aktiv", "answer": "active, sakriya, chatuvatikeyindiru", "options": ["necessary, required", "kannada: Sevane, consumption", "enmity, Vairatva", "active, sakriya, chatuvatikeyindiru"]}, {"numb": 72, "question": "Grundsatz", "answer": "Policy", "options": ["transparent, paradarhska", "usage  Kannada: BaLake,", "Policy", "violence, Himse, dourjanya"]}, {"numb": 73, "question": "Fl\u00e4che", "answer": "area, Bhoopradesha", "options": ["garbage", "area, Bhoopradesha", "combination", "approach, strategy"]}, {"numb": 74, "question": "Kommunikation", "answer": "communication", "options": ["communication", "permanent, shashwata", "defeat, solu", "prerequisites, \u0caa\u0cc2\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0caa\u0cc7\u0c95\u0ccd\u0cb7\u0cbf\u0ca4\u0c97\u0cb3\u0cc1"]}, {"numb": 75, "question": "Vertrieb", "answer": "marketing", "options": ["Blessings, verb is SegNen", "compulsory", "impaired, disabled", "marketing"]}, {"numb": 76, "question": "Abteilung", "answer": "department, ilaakhe", "options": ["improvment", "dignified", "department, ilaakhe", "Carbon monooxide"]}, {"numb": 77, "question": "grunds\u00e4tzlich", "answer": "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "options": ["forever, shashwata", "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "compulsory", "violent, himsatmaka"]}, {"numb": 78, "question": "Friedlich", "answer": "peaceful, shaantiyuta", "options": ["according to..", "serious, Gambhira", "communication", "peaceful, shaantiyuta"]}, {"numb": 79, "question": "Abdruck", "answer": "imprint, kaalachchu, Mudre", "options": ["involvement", "imprint, kaalachchu, Mudre", "imemdiately, tatkshana", "approach, strategy"]}, {"numb": 80, "question": "n\u00f6tig", "answer": "necessary, required", "options": ["fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "involvement", "necessary, required", "Victory, Jaya"]}, {"numb": 81, "question": "Behindert", "answer": "impaired, disabled", "options": ["peaceful, shaantiyuta", "active, sakriya, chatuvatikeyindiru", "Occupation", "impaired, disabled"]}, {"numb": 82, "question": "unmittelbar", "answer": "immediate, takshanavagi", "options": ["violent, himsatmaka", "immediate, takshanavagi", "forever, shashwata", "joyful, santoshita"]}, {"numb": 83, "question": "ewig", "answer": "forever, shashwata", "options": ["Carbon", "forever, shashwata", "KaruNe, Daye", "involvement"]}, {"numb": 84, "question": "Verfahren", "answer": "Procedure", "options": ["affected, concerned, baadhitha", "Procedure", "KaruNe, Daye", "attentive"]}, {"numb": 85, "question": "Freudig", "answer": "joyful, santoshadayaka", "options": ["joyful, nagumogada", "joyful, santoshadayaka", "defeat, solu", "joy, santosha"]}, {"numb": 86, "question": "Hectisch", "answer": "Hectic", "options": ["Hectic", "non violence, ahimse", "deadly", "department, vibhaga"]}, {"numb": 87, "question": "politisch", "answer": "political, raajakiya", "options": ["political, raajakiya", "communication", "spokesperson, vaktaar", "constantly, nirantaravagi"]}, {"numb": 88, "question": "Verbesserung", "answer": "improvment", "options": ["strategy", "Covert (Religion)", "joyful, nagumogada", "improvment"]}, {"numb": 89, "question": "Umweltfreundlich", "answer": "Enviornment friendly", "options": ["need, Avashyakate", "Enviornment friendly", "Cheat, Vanchane, Mosa", "Guideline, Kannada: Maargasoochi"]}, {"numb": 90, "question": "Segen", "answer": "Blessings, verb is SegNen", "options": ["attention, Gamana", "Blessings, verb is SegNen", "humanity", "communication"]}, {"numb": 91, "question": "Gewaltlosigkeit", "answer": "non violence, ahimse", "options": ["abuse, DurbaLake", "non violence, ahimse", "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "improvment"]}, {"numb": 92, "question": "Friede", "answer": "peace, shaanti", "options": ["Victory, Jaya", "peace, shaanti", "suddenly, idakiddante, akaasmat", "permanent, shashwata"]}, {"numb": 93, "question": "laut + dativ, laut + gen", "answer": "according to..", "options": ["according to..", "peace, shaanti", "Former, maaji", "illegal, kanoonu bahira"]}, {"numb": 94, "question": "vorsicht", "answer": "caution, precaution, ecchara, jagarookate", "options": ["caution, precaution, ecchara, jagarookate", "Hate, Dwesha", "logic, tarka", "Oxygen"]}, {"numb": 95, "question": "\ufeffGlobalizierung", "answer": "Globalization", "options": ["Globalization", "contact person, samparka vyakti", "Counter argument", "Fuel, Indhana"]}, {"numb": 96, "question": "Vorgehensweise", "answer": "approach, strategy", "options": ["Procedure", "process, kannada: prakriye", "combination", "approach, strategy"]}, {"numb": 97, "question": "gem\u00e4\u00df+dativ", "answer": "according to..", "options": ["temporary, taatkalika", "Counter argument", "illegal, kanoonu bahira", "according to.."]}, {"numb": 98, "question": "ehemalig", "answer": "Former, maaji", "options": ["Modernization", "resource, sampanmoola", "area, Kshetra", "Former, maaji"]}, {"numb": 99, "question": "Verlauf", "answer": "process, kannada: prakriye", "options": ["available, kannada : Labhyavide, Doraku", "logic, tarka", "Occupation", "process, kannada: prakriye"]}, {"numb": 100, "question": "Einsamkeit", "answer": "loneliness", "options": ["according to..", "loneliness", "affected, concerned, baadhitha", "spokesperson, vaktaar"]}, {"numb": 101, "question": "st\u00e4ndig", "answer": "constantly, nirantaravagi", "options": ["Carbon monooxide", "constantly, nirantaravagi", "Cheat, Vanchane, Mosa", "joyful, nagumogada"]}, {"numb": 102, "question": "widerlich", "answer": "ashyakara, disgusting", "options": ["adjective, Perfect, paripoorna", "ashyakara, disgusting", "process, kannada: prakriye", "Infrastructure"]}, {"numb": 103, "question": "absichtlich", "answer": "purposefully, uddeshapporvakavagi", "options": ["reluctant, manasillada", "forever, shashwata", "purposefully, uddeshapporvakavagi", "opposition,"]}, {"numb": 104, "question": "Nutzung", "answer": "Kannda: BaLake", "options": ["Kannda: BaLake", "marketing", "Nature", "abuse, DurbaLake"]}, {"numb": 105, "question": "Freundschaft", "answer": "friendship", "options": ["usage  Kannada: BaLake,", "Infrastructure", "friendship", "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi"]}, {"numb": 106, "question": "Treibhauseffekt", "answer": "Greenhouse effekt", "options": ["particular, nirdishtavada", "Greenhouse effekt", "obstacle, ade tade", "Hectic"]}, {"numb": 107, "question": "Kohlenstoffmonoxid", "answer": "Carbon monooxide", "options": ["garbage", "Carbon monooxide", "Procedure", "Nature"]}, {"numb": 108, "question": "Genehmigung", "answer": "approval", "options": ["carbon dioxide", "approval", "torture, chitrahimse", "Hectic"]}, {"numb": 109, "question": "sicht", "answer": "sight, drushti", "options": ["compulsory", "sight, drushti", "sarasari", "Blessings, verb is SegNen"]}, {"numb": 110, "question": "Fortschritt", "answer": "abhivraddhi, progress", "options": ["abhivraddhi, progress", "attentive", "necessary, required", "forever, shashwata"]}, {"numb": 111, "question": "einwandfrei", "answer": "adjective, Perfect, paripoorna", "options": ["compulsory", "Fuel, Indhana", "contact person, samparka vyakti", "adjective, Perfect, paripoorna"]}, {"numb": 112, "question": "Fr\u00f6hlich", "answer": "joyful, nagumogada", "options": ["compulsory", "caution, precaution, ecchara, jagarookate", "joyful, nagumogada", "affected, concerned, baadhitha"]}, {"numb": 113, "question": "befristet", "answer": "temporary, taatkalika", "options": ["sight, drushti", "Enviornment friendly", "temporary, taatkalika", "obstacle, ade tade"]}, {"numb": 114, "question": "Gebiet", "answer": "area, Kshetra", "options": ["area, Kshetra", "prerequisites, \u0caa\u0cc2\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0caa\u0cc7\u0c95\u0ccd\u0cb7\u0cbf\u0ca4\u0c97\u0cb3\u0cc1", "carbon dioxide", "Policy"]}, {"numb": 115, "question": "Modernizierung", "answer": "Modernization", "options": ["Cheat, Vanchane, Mosa", "Modernization", "process, kannada: prakriye", "joy, santosha"]}, {"numb": 116, "question": "Ernst", "answer": "serious, Gambhira", "options": ["according to..", "overview, pakshinota, avalokana", "Riot, galabhe", "serious, Gambhira"]}, {"numb": 117, "question": "Herausforderung", "answer": "Challenge", "options": ["active, sakriya, chatuvatikeyindiru", "violence, Himse, dourjanya", "Challenge", "communal, komu"]}, {"numb": 118, "question": "Verwendung", "answer": "usage  Kannada: BaLake,", "options": ["dignified", "Victory, Jaya", "usage  Kannada: BaLake,", "violent, himsatmaka"]}, {"numb": 119, "question": "Kohlenstoffdioxid", "answer": "carbon dioxide", "options": ["serious, Gambhira", "carbon dioxide", "area, Kshetra", "communication"]}, {"numb": 120, "question": "Einsam", "answer": "lonely", "options": ["approach, strategy", "lonely", "joyful, nagumogada", "necessary, required"]}, {"numb": 121, "question": "Kombination", "answer": "combination", "options": ["obstacle, ade tade", "Infrastructure", "combination", "improvment"]}, {"numb": 122, "question": "dauerhaft", "answer": "permanent, shashwata", "options": ["communication", "Nature", "permanent, shashwata", "combination"]}, {"numb": 123, "question": "W\u00fcrde", "answer": "dignity, Ghanathe", "options": ["KaruNe, Daye", "Fuel, Indhana", "involvement", "dignity, Ghanathe"]}, {"numb": 124, "question": "bestimmt", "answer": "particular, nirdishtavada", "options": ["dignified", "temporary, taatkalika", "particular, nirdishtavada", "waste, garbage"]}, {"numb": 125, "question": "der Hass", "answer": "Hate, Dwesha", "options": ["Pressure", "improvment", "joyful, santoshadayaka", "Hate, Dwesha"]}, {"numb": 126, "question": "erforderlich", "answer": "necessary, required", "options": ["opinion, view, abhipraya, nota", "necessary, required", "approval", "usage  Kannada: BaLake,"]}, {"numb": 127, "question": "Natur", "answer": "Nature", "options": ["non violence, ahimse", "Nature", "Victory, Jaya", "necessary, required"]}, {"numb": 128, "question": "Aufmerksam", "answer": "attentive", "options": ["process, kannada: prakriye", "Victory, Jaya", "dignified", "attentive"]}, {"numb": 129, "question": "Zustand state, condition, sthithi", "answer": "No response given", "options": ["No response given", "kannada: Sevane, consumption", "approach, strategy", "Challenge"]}, {"numb": 130, "question": "Vorgang", "answer": "process, kannada: prakriye", "options": ["sight, drushti", "Kannda: BaLake", "process, kannada: prakriye", "Guideline, Kannada: Maargasoochi"]}, {"numb": 131, "question": "obligatorisch", "answer": "compulsory", "options": ["Carbon", "attentive", "caution, precaution, ecchara, jagarookate", "compulsory"]}, {"numb": 132, "question": "grundlegend", "answer": "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "options": ["sign", "usage  Kannada: BaLake,", "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "Globalization"]}, {"numb": 133, "question": "\u00e4hnlich", "answer": "similar, holuva, samavada", "options": ["fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "illegal, kanoonu bahira", "humanity", "similar, holuva, samavada"]}, {"numb": 134, "question": "Beteiligung", "answer": "involvement", "options": ["involvement", "pramaanikarisida, dhrudikarisida", "political, raajakiya", "humanity"]}, {"numb": 135, "question": "Kommunal", "answer": "communal, komu", "options": ["attentive", "communal, komu", "necessary, required", "impaired, disabled"]}, {"numb": 136, "question": "Abfall", "answer": "waste, garbage", "options": ["Carbon monooxide", "Fuel, Indhana", "waste, garbage", "permanent, shashwata"]}, {"numb": 137, "question": "Fahrzeug", "answer": "vehicle, vaahana", "options": ["peaceful, shaantiyuta", "defeat, solu", "process, kannada: prakriye", "vehicle, vaahana"]}, {"numb": 138, "question": "notwending", "answer": "necessary, required", "options": ["ashyakara, disgusting", "prerequisites, \u0caa\u0cc2\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0caa\u0cc7\u0c95\u0ccd\u0cb7\u0cbf\u0ca4\u0c97\u0cb3\u0cc1", "carbon dioxide", "necessary, required"]}, {"numb": 139, "question": "Gegengrund", "answer": "Counter argument", "options": ["Krama, Measure", "Counter argument", "opposition,", "Digitalization"]}, {"numb": 140, "question": "widerstand", "answer": "resist, virdoshisu, tadedu nillisu", "options": ["Nature", "resist, virdoshisu, tadedu nillisu", "puprose, uddeesha", "dignified"]}, {"numb": 141, "question": "Chaos", "answer": "Kaavos, Kannda: Gondala", "options": ["spokesperson, vaktaar", "operations, business, firm", "obstacle, ade tade", "Kaavos, Kannda: Gondala"]}, {"numb": 142, "question": "Ansprechpartner", "answer": "contact person, samparka vyakti", "options": ["illegal, kanoonu bahira", "affected, concerned, baadhitha", "resist, virdoshisu, tadedu nillisu", "contact person, samparka vyakti"]}, {"numb": 143, "question": "Niederlage", "answer": "defeat, solu", "options": ["defeat, solu", "Enviornment friendly", "process, kannada: prakriye", "involvement"]}, {"numb": 144, "question": "Erfolg", "answer": "Victory, Jaya", "options": ["violent, himsatmaka", "serious, Gambhira", "Nature", "Victory, Jaya"]}];